export const verbPracticeDataPortugues = {
  2: [
    { prompt: "Eu", answer: "sou" },
    { prompt: "Tu", answer: "és" },
    { prompt: "Ele", answer: "é" },
    { prompt: "Ela", answer: "é" },
    { prompt: "Isso", answer: "é" },
    { prompt: "sou", answer: "eu" },
    { prompt: "és", answer: "tu" },
    { prompt: "é", answer: "ele/ela/isso" }
  ],
  3: [
    { prompt: "Eu", answer: "tenho" },
    { prompt: "Tu", answer: "tens" },
    { prompt: "Ele", answer: "tem" },
    { prompt: "Ela", answer: "tem" },
    { prompt: "tenho", answer: "eu" },
    { prompt: "tens", answer: "tu" },
    { prompt: "tem", answer: "ele/ela" }
  ]
};
